This fall, eerie greenish glow.
Scooby-Doo and the Alien Invaders is a animation, family,
comedy film directed by Jim Stenstrum.
A cosmic case of flying saucers, intergalactic intrigue and
out-of-this-world romance launches Scooby-Doo!
and the Mystery Inc., Gang into their most unearthly adventure ever.
Scooby Doo / Shaggy (voice), played by Scott Innes.
Daphne Blake  (voice), played by Mary Kay Bergman.
Velma Dinkley (voice), played by B.J. Ward.
Fred Jones (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Crystal / Amber (voice), played by Candi Milo.
Sergio / Buck (voice), played by Neil Ross.
Scooby-Doo and the Alien Invaders is a 2000 American direct-to-video
animated science fiction romantic comedy mystery film.
It is the third direct-to-video film based on
Scooby-Doo Saturday morning cartoons.
The film was produced by Warner Bros.
Animation in association with Hanna-Barbera.
It is the third of the first four Scooby-Doo direct-to-video films to be
animated overseas by Japanese animation studio Mook Animation.
Unlike the previous films and despite the grimmer
atmosphere, it has a lighter tone.
It is the last film to feature Mary Kay Bergman as the voice of Daphne,
following her death in November 1999, and was dedicated in her memory.
It is also the last film that longtime Scooby-Doo writer Glenn Leopold would
write before leaving due to "creative differences" from Warner Bros.
Additionally, it is the last film in the franchise to use cel animation, as starting with
Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase, the films would utilize digital ink and paint.
The film explores themes of earth, gold mine, alien, middle of nowhere.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and mind_bending.